原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛   一只虾   Silence
翻译     吃冰棒   酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     今  没有影子
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季第十三集
我们新的最受欢迎的保险代理
Our new favorite insurance agency!
我的天  拳击新星  就是你了
Oh, my, God, Battling Bud, you're the man!
看来你们这一晚上动静不小啊
Looks like you boys made quite a night of it.
道吉  你可能该给你太太打电话了
Dougie, you might want to call your wife.
太太
Wife?
布什内尔  我们是带着礼物来的
Bushnell, we come bearing gifts,
表达我们对你的感激之情
tokens of our gratitude to you.
这都是什么
What is all this?
一盒基度山二号
A box of Montecristo Number Twos.
真好
Oh, nice.
一对...
A set...
有印字的钻石袖扣
of monogrammed diamond cuff links.
真漂亮
Oh, they're beautiful.
还有你新车的钥匙
And the keys to your new car!
一辆宝马敞篷车
A BMW convertible.
现在你和道吉的能配成一对了
Now you and Dougie have a matched set.
伙计们
Fellas...
我不知道该说什么了
I am speechless.
一个错误被纠正了
A wrong has been made right,
太阳明媚如初了
and the sun is shining bright.
谢谢  伙计们
Ah, thank you, fellas.
我不知道发生了什么  托德先生
I-I have no idea what happened, Mr. Todd.
这可太不幸了
Well, this is most unfortunate.
我同意  我不知道能说什么了
I agree. I don't know what to say.
可你知道该怎么做
But you know what to do.
我们说过这事了
We talked about this.
我给你一天时间
I am giving you one day
去扭转局面
to remedy this situation.
可你之前说的是两天
But you said two before.
就一天
One day.
明白了吗
Do we have a complete understanding?
明白了  先生
Yes, sir.
罗杰
Roger.
罗杰  请进来一下
Roger, get in here, please.
稍等
Hold on just a minute.
琼斯太太吗
Mrs. Jones?
是的
Yeah?
你希望安装在哪
Uh, where do you want it set up?
什么
W-what?
桑尼·吉姆的新游乐设施
Sonny Jim's new gym set,
米彻姆兄弟的礼物
courtesy of the Mitchum brothers.
那车也是吗
And the car, too?
米彻姆兄弟的礼物
Mitchum brothers.
你想把游乐设施放哪
Where do you want the gym?
后院吧
Backyard?
好的  伙计们
All right. Guys!
我们走  后院
Let's go. The backyard.
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
昨晚你没回家
When you didn't come home last night,
我想到了最糟的可能性
I thought the worst.
看看你都干了什么
Look what you've done.
桑尼·吉姆都快高兴死了
Sonny Jim's in seventh heaven.
高兴死了
Seven heaven.
还有那车
And then the car...
道吉
Oh, Dougie...
我真是爱死你了
I love you so much.
西蒙大拿州
该死
Fuck.
操
怎么了  雷
What's the problem, Ray?
我明明把那家伙杀了
I killed that guy.
他就是我跟你说的那人
He's the one I told you about.
看来你没杀得太彻底啊  雷
You didn't kill him too good, Ray.
这次一定彻底
I will now.
雷  你在这里吗
Hey, Ray, you in here somewhere?
他怎么弄到密码的
And how did he get the code?
我给他的
I gave it to him.
我来看看你  伙计
Came to see you, buddy.
但只给了门的密码
But only to the door.
所以他被困住了
So he's trapped.
他是我的了
And mine.
好吧
All right.
我会把他留给你
I'll let you have him.
但我想先跟他玩玩
I want to have some fun with him first.
把他带上来
Bring him up!
进电梯
Get in the elevator.
把枪放下  雷
Put the gun away, Ray.
这里什么情况
What do we have here?
我来看我的朋友雷
I came to see my friend Ray.
我在这里
I'm here,
你这混蛋
you fuck.
冷静点  雷
Settle down, Ray.
看来我们有个新的竞争者了
Looks like we got ourselves a new contestant here.
跟他说说规矩  穆迪
Tell him how it works, Muddy.
很简单
Real simple.
这位是我们的老大
This man is our boss...
因为没人能在扳手腕比赛中赢过他
'cause no one can beat him at arm wrestling.
想象一下  那么多尝试过的人
Imagine all the men who've tried.
太多太多了
Many, many.
14年了
In 14 years,
没人有过一丁点胜算
no one's ever even come close.
任何新来的人都能有一次机会
Any new guy gets one chance.
就一次
One chance.
如果输了
And if you lose,
伦佐就成为你的老大
Renzo's your boss.
你可以现在离开
So you can leave now.
如果你留下  然后输了
If you stay and lose
却不按伦佐说的做
and you do not do what Renzo says...
你就会死
you die.
你自己决定吧
So you decide.
是否留下比赛  决定权在你
You stay and play the game. It's your choice.
瞧瞧你那样
Looking at you,
我觉得你还是走吧
I'd say you better leave.
这里算什么
What is this,
托儿所吗
kindergarten?
幼儿园
Nursery school?
如果我赢了呢
What do I get if I win?
那你就成为我们的老大
Then you'd be our boss.
我可不想当你们的老大
I don't want to be your boss.
但我如果赢了  我要他
But if I win, I want him.
请进来
Step inside.
咱们比一场吧
Let's play the game.
这是幼儿园老师送你的
That was from the nursery-school teacher.
坐
Sit down.
规则
Rules!
起始位置
Starting position.
比赛的手放在桌上
Wrestling arm on table.
真不知道他要怎么死
Doesn't know what he got into.
另一只手不能触碰桌子
Other hand cannot touch table.
举起手来
Hands up!
握紧
Grip!
我说开始才能开始
Do not start until I say.
你准备好了吗  老大
You ready, boss?
准备好了
Ready.
你呢
You ready?
准备好了
Ready.
看看他
Look at him.
他准备好了
Yeah, he's ready.
他害怕了
He's not ready.
开始掰手腕
Commence arm wrestle!
还没到底
Ain't touching yet!
干掉他
Take him out!
快扳倒他
Take him down!
起始位置
Starting positions.
快啊
Come on.
-快点啊  老大  -老大  你还愣着干嘛
- Come on, boss. - Boss, what are you doing?
加把劲  别玩了  老大
Come on, stop playing around, boss.
在起始位置舒服多了
Starting position's more comfortable.
快点啊  兄弟
Come on, man!
加油  老大  搞定他
Come on, boss! Get him!
你他妈别动  雷
Don't you fucking move, Ray!
-加油  -赶紧的  老大
- Oh, come on. - Come on, boss.
继续啊  扳倒他  掰过来
Bring it back, bring it back, bring it back.
-加油  快啊
- Come on, come on.
你掰到这位置时我的手有点不舒服
It hurt my arm when you moved it down here.
到这个位置是真的很痛
But it really hurt when you had it down here.
感受到了吗
See?
我把你的手掰到这位置是不是不舒服
Doesn't that hurt your arm when I go like that?
我想这样会更痛
I think it's much worse when it's down here.
操
Ah, fuck.
还是回到起始位置吧
Let's go back to starting positions.
真的舒服太多了
It's really much more comfortable.
干掉他
Take him out now!
你最好是待着别动
You best stay here.
-干掉他  -快啊
- Finish him! - Come on!
搞定他
Take him out!
卧槽
Oh, shit!
抓住他
Grab him.
站好  站好
Stand up, stand up.
-站好  别动  -操
- Stand up, stay there. - Shit.
他任你处置  老大
He's all yours, boss.
给我些手机
Give me some cell phones.
这里接收不到信号的  老大
Y-you're not gonna get any reception up here, boss.
雷和我要单独谈谈
Ray and I are gonna need some privacy.
他是你的了  老大
He's all yours, boss.
我们可以谈谈这个吗
Can we talk about this?
现在我们可以谈谈了
Now we can talk.
你需要钱吗
Do you need any money?
不需要
No.
有人雇你来杀我
Somebody hired you to kill me.
是谁
Who is it?
我有让你开口的方法
I can make you tell me.
我知道
I know it.
一个叫菲利普·杰弗里斯的人吩咐的
It came through a man named Phillip Jeffries.
至少这是他告诉我的名字
At least that's the name he gives.
我没见过他
I never met him.
我只跟他在电话里聊过
I only talked to him on the phone.
继续说
Keep talking.
他跟墨菲典狱长策划这一切
He set the whole prison thing up with Warden Murphy.
杰弗里斯说你会杀了我的
Jeffries says you were gonna kill me.
他说如果我先把你杀了  就可以出狱
He said I could get out and stay out if I killed you first.
为什么
Why?
他说你身上有他们想要的东西
He said that you got something inside that they want.
他有提过布里格斯少校吗
Did he ever mention Major Briggs?
没有
No.
放轻松  雷
Easy, Ray.
我又没拿枪
You know I don't have a gun.
我要给你看样东西
I got to show you something.
杰弗里斯原本吩咐我
Jeffries said I was supposed to put this on you...
杀了你之后把这东西放你身上
after I killed you.
你从哪得来的
Where did you get that?
就是在我走出牢房见到你之前
It was given to me...
拿到这东西的
right before I walked out of my cell and saw you.
谁给你的
Who gave it to you?
一个门卫
A guard.
我也不知道
I don't know.
他穿着门卫的衣服  但我从没见过他
He was dressed as a guard, but I'd never seen him before.
把它戴在  无名指上  左手
Put it on-- ring finger, left hand.
现在
Now...
你知道我想要什么的  雷
you know what I want, Ray.
你想要我从黑斯廷斯得到的坐标吗
You want the coordinates I got from Hastings?
还是  他那美女秘书  贝蒂
Rather, his pretty secretary, Betty?
你真以为我会告诉你吗
Do you really think I'm gonna give them to you?
你真觉得我给你的数字可信吗
You really think you could even trust the numbers I give you?
我知道你谁
I know who you are.
我可以伸手进口袋吗
Can I reach in my pocket?
那要看看里面是什么
Depends on what's in the pocket.
数字啊  笨
The numbers, stupid.
我把那些坐标都写了出来
I have the coordinates written out.
它们就在我口袋里
They're in my pocket.
给你
Here...
雷  菲利普·杰弗里斯在哪
Ray, where is Phillip Jeffries?
我不知道
I don't know.
雷  菲利普·杰弗里斯在哪
Ray, where's Phillip Jeffries?
我最近听说
Last I heard,
他在一个叫荷兰人的地方
he was at a place called The Dutchman's,
但这不是一个真的地方名
but it's not a real place.
我知道是什么
I know what it is.
拉斯维加斯城市警察局
不  你开过了
No. You went too far.
大概是两个街口
It's--it's about two blocks back.
掉个头
Try to make a U-turn.
很好  然后
Okay, then jus--
绕回那个街口  你刚刚路过了
Go around the block. You just missed it.
好的  我会跟他说的
Yeah. I'll tell him.
好  再见  母亲
All right. Bye, Mom.
小心驾驶
Drive careful.
母亲叫我们周日去吃晚餐
Mom wants us to come to Sunday dinner.
希望这个周末能顺顺利利
Hopes there's no murders this weekend.
又要长胖了
Fat chance that's gonna happen.
她不能在这撒尿
She can't piss on the floor!
快带她走
Get her out of here!
她还在尿尿  菲尔
She's still pissing, Phil.
狗杂种  我要喂你吃屎
Cocksuckers! I'll shit in your mouth!
我来搞定她
I'll get her.
她有刀
And she's got a knife!
去你的  傻逼
Fuck you, Twinkies!
我要把你给阉了
I'll cut your nuts off!
电她  电她
Tase her, tase her!
菲利  电她
Phil, tase her!
把她弄出去
Get her out of here.
拿到道格拉斯·琼斯的指纹了
Got the prints on our pal Douglas Jones.
指纹识别系统显示  两天前
According to AFIS, he escaped
他从南达科他州的一间重刑犯监狱越狱了
from a high-security prison in South Dakota two days ago.
-什么  -不  好戏在后头
- What? - No, it gets better.
他是一名失踪的联调局探员
He's a missing FBI agent.
那
That...
那是个天大的错误
That's a huge fucking mistake!
什么
What?
-赌一块钱吗  -来吧
- A dollar? - Oh, go for it.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
好
Sure.
好吧
All right, all right.
打扰一下
Ex-- excuse me?
我想找克拉克警探
I-I'm looking for Detective Clark.
他在后面抽烟
Yeah, he's out back, grabbing a smoke.
从这道门穿过去
Just through the doors.
好
Okay.
操
F-fuck.
-你来干吗  -我要问你一个问题
- What are you doing? - I need to ask you a question.
你知道你不该来这里
You know you're not supposed to come here.
我必须问你一个问题
I have to ask you a question.
最好不是废话
Better be good.
不是
It is.
我要知道一种没法查出来的
I need to know a good poison I could use--
毒药
undetectable.
你个混蛋
You shit.
什么
What?
乌头碱
Aconitine.
取证实验室变聪明了
Crime labs are getting wise to it,
但那是你最好的办法
but it's your best bet.
在哪能找到
Where do I get it?
付我高价就能找到  小子
By paying me top fucking dollar, cowboy.
你为什么这么针对我
Why are you so against me?
因为你是个软弱无能的胆小鬼
'Cause you're a weak fucking coward.
光看到你就让我倒胃口
It makes me sick just to look at you.
我在尽力不让整项行动瓦解
I'm trying to keep this whole operation from falling apart.
有人盯上我们了  所以我需要那些东西
Somebody's onto us. That's why I need the stuff.
这你得花点钱了
It's gonna cost you.
五
Five...
千块
thousand.
就能搞定
It'll do the job,
给你两小时的时候离开
give you two hours to get away.
对你这种胆小鬼完全足够了
It's perfect for a chickenshit punk like you.
我会把钱弄来的
I'll get the money.
今晚九点半
Nine-thirty tonight,
克罗斯利家后门
outside of Crosley's, at the back door.
怎么了
What's up?
他要按耐不住了
He's cracking.
那混蛋想要毒害某人
The fuck wants to poison somebody.
我打给托德先生
I'll call Mr. Todd.
好
Yeah.
犹他州
Utah.
摩门教徒
Mormons.
他们不喝酒
They don't drink liquor.
不喝咖啡
They don't drink coffee.
不喝可乐
They don't drink Coca-Cola.
而且
And...
他们甚至不会在婚前发生性行为
they don't even have sex before marriage.
但是在他们结婚的时候
Yeah, but when they do get married,
我听说他们
I heard they-- they can marry, like,
能娶六或十个女人
six or ten women.
好笑的是他们的人只有这么点
Funny there's not more of them.
我猜是因为酒的原因
I guess it's the drinks.
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
早上好  道吉
Good morning, Dougie.
一杯醇香的热咖啡怎么样
What do you say to a nice hot cup of coffee?
咖啡
Coffee.
我请你
It's on me.
给道吉·琼斯来杯上好的咖啡
Coffee for the great Dougie Jones.
道吉·琼斯
Dougie Jones.
西蒙极品咖啡店
咖啡来了
Here you go.
亲爱的  要来点樱桃派吗
Hon, you want some cherry pie?
樱桃派
Cherry pie.
去坐吧  我给你拿一块过去
Go sit down. I'll bring you a slice.
好好去享受你的咖啡吧
Go enjoy your coffee.
咖啡
Coffee.
别担心
Don't worry about it, okay?
道吉
Dougie...
你的咖啡在这
there's your coffee.
你的咖啡
Your coffee.
天呐
Oh, God!
很对不起  我从没想要伤害任何人
So sorry. I never meant to hurt anyone.
你的樱桃派来了
Here's your cherry pie.
这么难喝啊
That bad, huh?
道吉
Dougie!
道吉  很对不起
Dougie, I'm so sorry!
很对不起
So sorry!
咖啡店
贝基
Hey, Becky.
妈
Mom...
史蒂文昨晚没回家
Steven never came home last night.
他已经不见了两个晚上
That's two nights that he's been gone.
两天了  妈
That's two days, Mom.
很遗憾  亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
我真的很担心
I'm really worried.
也许他只是需要点时间
Well, maybe he just needs some time.
我不知道  我觉得他出了什么严重的事
I don't know. I think he's going through something bad.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
亲爱的  我们能晚点再说吗
Okay, honey, can we talk about this later?
很多饥肠辘辘的客人
Hungry customers.
好
Sure.
不  不如这样吧
No, you know what?
不如你过来这里
Why don't you come down here,
我给你来一块美味的樱桃派
and I'm gonna serve you up a beautiful piece of cherry pie,
一勺香草冰淇淋
a scoop of vanilla ice cream,
还有很多的鲜奶油
and lots of whipped cream.
真要命  好吧
Oh... damn, okay.
听起来真不错  好吧
That sounds so good. Okay.
好  我一会儿到
Okay, I'll be right there.
好  快点  我们找时间聊聊  好吗
Okay, hurry up, and we'll find some time to talk, okay?
好  谢谢  我爱你
Okay, thanks. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我...
I--
不敢相信我犯了...
I can't believe what I've don--
不敢相信我成了这种人
I can't believe what I've become.
我企图给道吉下毒
I tried poisoning Dougie.
他一眼就识穿了  天呐
He saw right through me. Oh, God.
他是如此宽宏大量
He was so kind about it.
不敢相信我想干出这等苟且之事
I can't believe what I was about to do.
我一定要认错
I have to confess.
认错
Confess.
我会的  道吉
I will, Dougie.
我会的
I will.
布什内尔...
Bushnell...
好几个月来
I've been selling you down the river
我一直都在为邓肯·托德出卖你
for months and months for Duncan Todd.
我一直在给托德做事
I've been working for Todd.
我...
I--
我撒了谎  骗了钱
I've lied and cheated for money.
安东尼...
Anthony...
道吉已经告诉我了
Dougie already showed me.
他已经把这些全都告诉我了
He explained all this already.
真的吗
He did?
既然你已经认错了
Now that you're confessing,
不得不说我对你的愤怒
I have to admit that my anger,
还有鄙视正在平息
my contempt for you is subsiding.
道吉甚至把自己搭进去了
Dougie even implicated himself.
他告诉我你是如何操控索赔单
And he showed me how you manipulated claims,
你让我失去了一大笔钱
and you cost me plenty.
我之前很信任你  安东尼
I trusted you, Anthony.
我视你为朋友
I looked at you as my friend
我的头牌销售顾问
and my number-one sales agent.
头牌销售顾问
Number-one sales agent.
我怎么能这样忽悠你
How can I make it up to you?
我对自己所作所为感到无比羞愧
I'm so ashamed of what I've done.
要不是道吉
And if it weren't for Dougie,
我可能就成了一个杀人犯了
I might have a murder on my hands.
天啊  我该怎么办
Oh, my God, what can I do?
我准备把你送走很长很长一段时间
I was prepared to send you away for a long, long time.
但现在...
But now...
你愿意指证邓肯·托德吗
are you prepared to testify against Duncan Todd?
愿意
Y-yes.
愿意  即使我会在这之间死掉
Yes, even if I die in the process.
我几星期没合眼
I haven't slept for weeks.
我还吐了血  我不能再这样生活下去了
I vomited blood. I can't live like this.
我只想死或者做出改变
I only want to die or change.
布什内尔  请帮帮我
Bushnell, please help me.
我只想重回正道
I only want to make things right again.
还有那两个道吉发现的警察呢
And these two cops that Dougie found?
什么  他连他们俩也都知道了
Wha-- He knows about them, too?
他们俩  也
Them, too.
他们比托德还要坏
They're worse than Todd.
你不知道你在问什么
You don't know what you're asking.
我其实不是在问你  安东尼
I'm not really asking, Anthony.
我只想弥补我犯下的错
I-I only want to fix this mess I made.
道吉救了我的命
Dougie saved my life.
谢谢你  道吉
Thank you, Dougie.
谢谢道吉
Thank Dougie.
谢谢你
Thank you.
双R餐厅
你最近还好吗
How are you?
你呢
还行吧
Hanging in.
给我来份老样子
I will have the usual.
好
Okay.
-一会就给你送过来  -谢谢
- Get that right up for you. - Thanks.
不客气
Yeah, no problem.
你好  诺玛
Hey, Norma.
雪莉已经回家了吗
Shelly go home already?
是的
Yeah, she did.
好吧
Oh, okay.
那就不打扰二位了
I'll leave you two.
不不  过来一起吃晚餐吧
No, no, come and have some dinner.
我刚点了  谢谢
I just ordered. Thanks.
博比  快给我坐过来
Bobby, get your butt back over here.
独自进餐可不好
It's no good eating alone.
谢谢
Thanks.
那...
So...
有什么新鲜事吗  副警长
What's new, Deputy?
我们今天找到了一些我爸留下的东西
Oh, well, we, uh, found some stuff that my dad left today.
-真的吗  -嗯
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
什么样的东西
What kind of stuff?
还不知道  但它...
Don't know yet, but it--
是个什么东西
something.
知道吗
You know?
谢谢
Thanks.
不过我们会查明的
We're gonna check it out, though.
我会告诉你结果的
I'll tell you that.
我去给你取餐  艾德
I'll go bring your dinner, Ed.
你希望我换个座位吗
Hey? You want me to move to another booth?
这样你们好...
So you guys can...?
没原因  伙计  这里不会发生什么
No reason, pal. Nothing happening here.
-给你  -谢谢你  宝贝
- There you go. - Thanks, babe.
你来了
Hey, you.
你好  亲爱的
Hey, girl.
你俩聊
You two talk business.
我们换个地方坐
We'll move somewhere else.
很高兴见到你  沃尔特
Good to see you, Walter.
我也很高兴见到你
Oh, yeah. Good to see you, too.
他叫什么来着
What's his name again?
艾德
Ed.
艾德·赫尔利
Ed Hurley.
对  是
Oh, right, yeah.
你看起来很美
You're looking beautiful.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
我该怎么感谢你呢
So, uh, to what do I owe this pleasure?
诺玛  我得开车去一趟
Norma, I had to make the drive
因为今早我拿到了上个月的报告
'cause I got last month's reports this morning,
我迫不及待想说给你听
and I was so excited to share them with you.
快说来听听
Tell me.
我们五家诺玛的双R分店中有三家
Three of our five Norma's Double R franchises
开始盈利了
turned a profit.
对这样一个新品牌来说这是个巨大的里程碑
And that's a huge milestone for such a new brand,
尤其目前整个地区的经济
particularly when this whole region
都还面临着艰巨的挑战
still faces such uphill challenges economically.
所以这是好消息吗
So that's good?
这是大好消息
That's very good.
看看这个...
Looking at what's...
奇怪的是
Curiously,
两个拖后腿的餐厅其中之一
one of the two that's lagging
就是这里
is this one right here--
你的旗舰店
your flagship diner.
现在这行情生意都会有点下滑的
Well, business always takes a little dip this time of year.
这已经持续几个月了
It's been going on for a few months now.
所以我擅自做了一个销售终端分析
So I took the liberty of running a point-of-sale analysis
将这里和其餐厅做了一个对比
between this location and the others.
我真的有点看不懂这个
I-I can't really decipher that.
你能直接告诉我这是什么意思吗
Could you just tell me what it means?
简单来说
In black and white,
你将派成本太高
you're spending too much per pie
收费不够
and not charging enough.
听着  沃尔特
Well, look, Walter,
我之前就想对你说  就是...
I wanted to say this to you before. It's--
我听别人说
I-I've heard from other people
他们觉得我们其它分店做的派
that they think that our pies at the other locations
没有我们这家好吃
are just not as good as the ones we have here.
我在听
I hear you.
但按照我们和每一家签的协议
And I gave them all my exact recipes,
我把全部的配方都给他们了
as per our agreement,
我觉得他们没有按照配方来
but I don't think they're following them.
诺玛  我向你保证
Norma, I assure you
他们完全是按你的配方来的  而且...
they're following your recipes to the letter, but also...
根据和每一家签的协议...
per the agreement...
他们可以自行决定在哪购买原料
Using their discretion about where they get the ingredients.
不对
Mm, no.
我所有的原料都是天然  有机的本地食材
All my ingredients are natural, organic, local.
我知道  你用爱在做这些派
I know. You make them with love.
但我们的协议就是如此
But this was our agreement.
诺玛...
Norma...
你是个真正的艺术家
you're a real artist.
但爱没法一直让我们盈利
But love doesn't always turn a profit.
我们百分之百相信你
We believe in you 100 percent,
但从商业角度来说
but from a business perspective,
董事会希望你能在不牺牲任何高标准的情况下
the board would like you to consider some alternatives
考虑下其它选择
without sacrificing any of the high standards
而这些标准正是你的金字招牌
that you're so well-known for.
好吧  要是你能说一下有哪些选择
Well, if you can explain the alternatives,
我会考虑一下的
I'll--I'll look into it.
我一点儿也不想泼你冷水
Well, look, I-I don't mean to sound discouraging one little bit.
这是个大好消息
This is all good news.
就是稍微调整下配方
It's just about tweaking the formula
维持菜品的高水准并保持盈利
to ensure consistency and profitability.
举个例子
For instance,
我们觉得现在应该把餐厅名字改为
we think it's really time you changed this name
诺玛的双R
to Norma's Double R.
知道吗  沃尔特  在双峰镇
You know, Walter, in Twin Peaks,
双R这个名字已经有50多年的历史了
it's been the Double R Diner for over 50 years,
这才是大家熟悉的名字
and that's how people know it.
双R是没有什么不好
No disrespect to the Double R,
但你会记起我们的市场调查表明
but you'll recall our market research showed
你的名字在大家心中反响更大
people responded so much more favorably to your name--
餐厅就应该叫诺玛的双R
Norma's Double R, as it should be.
你是分店的形象代言人
You're the face of the franchise.
待会共进晚餐吗
Are we on for dinner later?
庆祝
To celebrate?
是的  沃尔特
Yes, Walter.
那...
So...
好吧  为了防止...
Okay, so, just in case...
抱歉  我们打烊了
I'm sorry. We're closed.
天啊
Oh, my God!
雅各比医生
Dr. Jacoby.
娜丁
Nadine.
-是你吗  -是我
- Is that you? - It's me.
我能叫你安普博士吗
Can I call you Dr. Amp?
就是我
That's me.
我一般都会忽略后面
I usually leave out the back.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我太喜欢你的节目了
I love your show so much.
你为我做了太多
You have done so much for me.
我喜欢你的橱窗展示
Well, I love your-- your window display.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
-天啊  -你真的喜欢吗
- Oh, my God. - Do you really like it?
太了不起了
It--it's magnificent.
那些窗帘一点声音也没有
And those drapes are completely silent.
这是我在向你致敬  安普博士
This is my tribute to you, Dr. Amp.
多亏了你
Thanks to you,
我真的开始把自己从屎里铲出来
I am really starting to shovel myself out of the shit!
娜丁
Oh, Nadine.
这对我意义非凡
That--that just means the world to me.
真的
It really does.
你  知道吗  这...
You--you know, it's--
这是我们和他们之间的较量
it's us against them.
我就是最忠诚的步兵
And I am your most loyal foot soldier...
或者...
or...
铲屎官
shoveler.
知道吗   上次我见你
You know, the... last--last time I saw you,
都是大约七年前了
it was about seven years ago.
你...
You...
你趴在地上
You were down on your hands and knees,
找一个土豆
looking for a potato.
那时我在哪
Where was I?
在超市
It was, uh, you know, in the supermarket.
你弄掉了一个土豆
You--you had dropped it.
那天刮着大风暴
It--There was a... a big storm that day.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
看上去第一回合和第二回合就要开始了
Looks like, uh, round number one and two under way.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
他终于倒下了  紧握着绳子
And he finally goes down, hangs onto the ropes.
那位先生问他有没有事
Oh, the gentleman asks him if he's okay.
现在还是拳击比赛
Now it's a boxing match again.
右手打中了大个子的耳朵
Oh, the right hand catches the big guy by the ear!
她说了什么
What did she say?
奥黛丽
Audrey...
我们说好了的
we've been over this.
告诉我
Tell me!
奥黛丽
Audrey.
别闹了
Stop it.
我...
I d--
我觉得我自己根本不在这里
I feel like I'm somewhere else.
你有过这种感觉吗  查理
Have you ever had that feeling, Charlie?
没有
No.
感觉我在别处  感觉我不是自己
Like I'm somewhere else and--and like I'm somebody else.
你有过这种感觉吗
Have you ever felt that?
没有
No.
我感觉我一直是自己
I always feel like myself.
也许这并不算最好的状态
And it may not always be the best feeling.
我不知道我是谁  但我肯定不是我自己
Well, I'm not sure who I am, but I'm not me.
这是存在主义第一课
This is Existentialism 101.
操
Oh, fuck you!
我是认真的
I'm serious!
除了我自己  我还能相信谁
Who am I supposed to trust but myself?
我还不知道我自己是谁
And I don't even know who I am!
那我该怎么办
So what the fuck am I supposed to do?
你应该去酒馆
You're supposed to go to the Roadhouse
看看比利在不在那里
and see if Billy is there.
我想是的
I guess.
远吗
Is it far?
得了吧  奥黛丽  你知道在哪里
Come on, Audrey, you know where it is.
要不是我了解你  我肯定觉得你嗑药了
If I didn't know better, I would swear you were on drugs.
到底在哪里
Just where is it?
我送你去
I'm gonna take you there.
你还要继续玩下去吗
Now, are you gonna stop playing games,
还是说由我结束你编的故事
or do I have to end your story, too?
什么故事  查理
What story is that, Charlie?
是住在路口的小姑娘的故事吗
Is that the story of the little girl who lived down the lane?
是吗
Is it?
是你想去的
You're the one that wanted to go.
现在你看起来好像想留下来
Now you're looking like you want to stay.
我想留下也想走
I want to stay, and I want to go.
我都想
I want to do both.
选哪个  查理
Which will it be, Charlie?
你会选哪个
Which one would you be?
查理  帮帮我
Charlie, help me.
这里就像是鬼城
It's like Ghostwood here.
枪炮酒吧
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
酒馆为大家隆重欢迎
the Roadhouse is proud to welcome
詹姆斯·赫尔利
James Hurley.
*只有你*
*Just you*
*和我*
*And I*
*只有你*
*Just you*
*和我*
*And I*
*永远*
*Together*
*一起*
*Forever*
*相爱*
*In love*
*只有你*
*Just you*
*和我*
*And I*
*只有你*
*Just you*
*和我*
*And I*
*永远*
*Together*
*一起*
*Forever*
*相爱*
*In love*
*我们一起*
*We go strolling*
*巡回*
*Together*
*相爱*
*In love*